markethero.io 2018-08-30

# Market Hero Privacy Policy — Market Hero

##  Market Hero Privacy Policy

## (Last Revised: September 28, 2017)

Thank you for visiting the MarketHero.io web site (hereinafter “Website”). Market Hero, Limited, a St. Lucia limited liability company having offices in Dallas Texas, USA (hereinafter “We”) understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy, and this Privacy Policy describes how we use personal information that is collected at this Website.

Please read this Privacy Policy before using this Website or submitting any personal information. California residents, please also see the “Note To California Residents” section for additional rights that apply to you.

By using this Website, you accept the privacy practices contained in this Privacy Policy. These privacy practices may change from time to time, but any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy whenever you visit the Website to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

## 1\. Information We Collect

A. Personally Identifiable Information

In order to serve our customers, we collect personally identifiable information, like names, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, and sometimes credit card information when such information is voluntarily submitted by our visitors. We will only use your personal information for the following purposes: (1) to deliver the products and/or services to you that you have requested; (2) to validate your compliance with the terms and conditions; (3) for content improvement and feedback purposes; (4) to reach you, when necessary, regarding your use of the Website or product(s); and (5) for the few situations described below to better serve you.

Partners: In some cases we may provide services or sell product lines jointly with other businesses. For these co-branded offerings in which a third party is involved in your transactions, we will sometimes share or jointly collect customer information related to those transactions with that third party. On the co-branded registration pages we will state who is collecting or receiving the information and whose privacy statement governs its use so that you will know at the time you create your account exactly how your information will be used. If you are registered with Company through a partnership and you request to opt out of receiving promotional updates, in order to comply with the provisions in the CAN-SPAM Act, we will also provide your email address to that partner so that they may also discontinue sending you messages on behalf of Company.

Affiliated Entities: We may sometimes share or jointly collect information with our parent entity and the wholly owned subsidiaries and affiliated divisions of our parent company entity. Sharing this information helps us make your customer experience more seamless and efficient by allowing us to improve our marketing efforts to better target customer needs, streamline our processes and consolidate our backend business systems. In the event we are ever sold or acquired by a third party, we would also transfer your information as part of the business being sold to that third party.

Testimonials: With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us via one of the methods listed in the Contact Section of this Privacy Policy.

Email Usage: By submitting your email address on this Website, you agree to receive email from us. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do.

By submitting your email address, you also agree to allow us to use your email address for custom audience targeting on sites like Facebook, where we display custom advertising to specific people who have opted-in to receive communications from us.

Telephone: In addition, you agree that by submitting your telephone contact information on this Website and/or registering to receive the product and/or service offered herein, such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry, and/or an application for the purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (ATSR), 16 CFR ‘310 et seq. and any applicable state and local “do not call” regulations. We retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and the applicable state regulations.

Updating Your Personal Information: If you wish to change or review your personal information, go to your My Profile page. There you can access or update the personal information and account history we have on file. Please contact us support@MarketHero.com using the contact info in the Contacting Us section if you need assistance in updating or reviewing your information. We will respond to your request to review the information we have on file for you within 30 days.

B. Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We also may collect various types of non-personally identifiable information to help us make your experience more enjoyable, measure site activity to identify future improvements that should be made, and compile aggregate data to help serve site visitors better.

For example, we may use session and persistent “cookies,” session logs, web beacons, GIF/pixel tags, banner ads, third-party click tracking analytics tools (such as Google Analytics), third party retargeting networks that may display our advertisements to you on other sites that you visit to remind you about us, and third party networks that serve user-requested emails (e.g., for a refer-a-friend email) to collect non-personally identifiable or other aggregated information about site visitors.

To maintain our quality of service and to assist in the analysis of product performance, we may gather data on connection information, including the timing and size of all packets sent over the Internet during a session. The gathered information is used only to ensure the highest quality experience possible when using our products.

We continuously improve our websites and our products and we utilize different third party web analytics tools to help us do so. We are interested in how visitors use our websites, our desktop tools, our mobile applications, what they like and dislike, and where they have problems. Our products, desktop tools and mobile applications use analytical tools to understand feature usage patterns, to enhance and improve your product experience and offer you specific usage tips and guidance. In connection with normal business operations, as well as to increase functionality and enhance your user experience, this usage information may be linked to personal information that we have about individual users. We maintain ownership of this data and we do not share this type of data about individual users with third parties.

We may also conduct surveys and ask users to volunteer demographic information to be used on an aggregate basis for internal market research, presentation to advertisers and joint research projects with outside companies involved in product development. We use such information to better focus our product and personalize the scope of services offered to each individual user.

Cookies are text files that are used by your computer’s web browser to store your preferences, and enable us to enhance your user experience with our Website. Third party retargeting networks may also use cookies to display our advertisements to you on other sites. You can learn more about how to opt-out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.

Emails or newsletters that we send electronically may use techniques such as web beacons or pixel tags to gather email metrics and information to improve the reader’s experience, such as the number of emails that are opened, whether they were forwarded or printed, the type of device from which they were opened, and the location (e.g. city, state, and county) associated with the applicable IP address.

Our Site includes Social Media Features (often called an “Open ID”), such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. These services will also authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. These Services may give you the option to post information about your activities on our websites to your profile page to share with others within your network. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.We may track aggregate data about the number of visits to this Website with an open ID, the number of items “liked” on this Website, or items on this Website that you choose to share with a third-party social media site.Other parties such as advertising partners and analytics companies may also be collecting information about your online activity across various websites over time. The information collected by those third parties may include identifiers that allow those third parties to tailor the ads that they serve to your computer or other device. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret web browser-based “Do Not Track” signals other than cookies, we do not currently respond to “Do Not Track” signals that are undefined.

Please note that you do have the option to configure most web browsers to NOT accept cookies. However, be aware that disabling cookies may keep you from having access to some functions or services on our Website or the web-hosted software that runs on our Website.

## 2\. Third Party Actions

We do not control and are not liable for the actions of any third parties who we may promote and/or link to from this Website. We pride ourselves in recommending quality companies, but have no control over the actions of those third parties, the content they provide, or their privacy practices. While we are not liable for any of the actions of those third parties, you should feel free to give us feedback from time to time on your experiences with any third parties to whom we work with so that we may enhance our future service to all customers.

## 3\. Children’s Privacy

We do not knowingly intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under 18 years of age. If your minor child has provided us with personally identifiable information, you may contact us at the phone number or mailing address listed in the section entitled “Contacting Us” if you want this information deleted from our records. We will then make reasonable efforts to remove your child’s information from the database that stores the information.

## 4\. IP Addresses

We may use your IP address to help prevent fraud, to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather broad demographic information, and to offer you products and services.

## 5\. Commitment to Data Security

All information collected from you is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. Furthermore, employees, contractors, and vendors who have access to your personally identifiable information in connection with providing services for us are required to keep the information confidential.

We use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, and we do everything we can to protect user information offline. Unfortunately, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take reasonable measures to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of the information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

## 6\. Contacting Us

If you need to contact us, you can email us at support@MarketHero.com, or call us at (214) 295-2623.

We strive to provide excellent products, along with equally excellent customer service. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our practices, please feel free to contact us using one of the methods listed above.

## 7\. Severability

If any part of this Privacy Policy is held invalid or unenforceable, that portion shall be construed in a manner consistent with applicable law to reflect, as nearly as possible, the original intentions of the parties, and the remaining portions shall remain in full force and effect.

## 8\. Note To California Residents

If you live in the State of California, under the California Civil Code, you have the right to request that companies who conduct business in California provide you with a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed Personal Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes.

Alternatively, the law provides that if a company has a Privacy Policy that gives either an opt-out (often referred to as “unsubscribe”) or opt-in choice for use of your Personal Information by third parties (such as advertisers or affiliated companies) for marketing purposes, that the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options.

This Website qualifies for the alternative option; it has a comprehensive Privacy Policy and provides you with details on how you may either opt-out or opt-in to the use of your Personal Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes during the preceding year.

If you are a California resident and want to request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, you must send a request to the following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal mail). Please send an email to the Privacy Administrator at support@MarketHero.com.

All requests sent via email must be labeled "Your California Privacy Rights" on the email subject line clearly stated on the actual request. For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. Please include your zip code for our own recordkeeping.

We do not accept requests via the telephone, mail, or by facsimile. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.
